- Previously on Friends:
- I don't feel like I have a girlfriend.
You want me to quit my job so you
can feel like you have a girlfriend?
- Is this about Mark?
- Oh, my God.
- Okay, it's not.
I cannot keep having
the same fight with you!
Look, maybe we should
just take a break.
Fine. You're right.
Let's take a break.
Let's get some frozen yogurt
or something.
No.
A break from us.
Then we had this big, stupid fight,
and I said I wanted to take a break.
I don't want to take a break.
This is crazy.
Don't you think
we can work on this?
What do you want to drink?
Who's that?
Nobody.
Is that Mark?
Honey, look, he just...
Yeah. Got it!
Hey, come dance.
What, are you married?
Because that's okay.
How was the big anniversary dinner?
Well, we never actually got to dinner.
Nice.
No, we kind of broke up instead.
What?
My God, Monica!
It's on the ceiling!
That's okay.
This is more important than fruit...
...on my ceiling.
You broke up?
Yeah, but it's okay because
when Ross left, Mark came over.
- Oh, no! You and Mark?
- It's okay. Calm down.
Mark and I talked...
...and I realized how much
I love your stupid brother, and...
...yeah, we got our problems,
but I really wanna make it work.
Morning!
The One the Morning After
Hi, it's me. I've been trying
to reach you all night. I feel awful.
Please, Ross, you've gotta know
there's nothing between me and Mark.
This whole breakup thing
is just stupid.
I'm just so sorry I put you through it.
And I don't want to get
back together over a machine.
- So I love you.
- I love you.
And you know what?
I'm gonna go to bed now...
...but on my way to work tomorrow,
I'm gonna stop by around 8:30. Bye.
Chloe, how's it coming?
What kind of puppy do you think
I should get?
You know, I don't know.
How about a big one?
- But my apartment's so...
- Well, then a small one.
- Listen, we have to go.
- Wait! Where's my shoes?
You sure you need shoes?
Do I know why we're rushing?
Yeah, you know the girlfriend
I told you about?
Well, it turns out that she wants
to get back together with me.
I found it!
That's so great for you guys!
You must be so happy!
Yes, I am. One of the many
things I'm feeling.
- Good luck with your girlfriend.
- Oh, thank you.
- You got my message?
- You are right on time!
So, what do you say?
Can I be your girlfriend again?
Yes, you can. Very much.
- Why are you mopping your ceiling?
- There's banana on it.
I have the spirit of an
old Indian woman living in mine.
So then you know.
The mailman was downstairs,
so I brought up your mail.
- Oh, good. Thanks.
- Now, what is Fabutech?
All right, don't judge me
too much, okay?
But I saw this infomercial,
and I swear to you I have never, ever...
...bought anything on TV before.
Except for this mop.
But there was this stuff on leg-waxing.
It looked so amazing.
Waxine!
Yes! Have you seen it?
It's incredible!
I so want to be a Waxine Girl!
I know!
Do you think it really doesn't hurt?
Because how can they do that?
Hello! Organic substances recently
discovered in the depths of the rain forest?
They have the best stuff in there.
Oh, my God!
We figured when we couldn't find you,
you'd gone home to make up with Rachel.
Which is probably what
you should have done, huh?
You think?
God, I'm in hell.
I mean, what am I gonna do?
Rachel's all like, "I love you,"
and "Let's work on this"...
...and all I can think about...
...is what is she gonna do
when I tell her what I did?
Before we answer that, we should
address the more important question:
How dumb are you?
What? Look, we're trying to
rebuild a relationship here, right?
How am I supposed to do that
without being totally honest?
Ross, look, I'm onboard about
the total-honesty thing. I am.
Just not about stuff that's
gonna get you in trouble.
He's right. Nobody's gonna benefit,
and you're just gonna hurt her.
Yeah, and there won't be
a relationship left to rebuild.
Don't you think...?
Look, if you absolutely have to tell her,
at least wait till the timing's right.
And that's what deathbeds are for.
- Yeah, okay.
- All right.
Okay. Now, we just have to make sure
she doesn't find out some other way.
Did you think about the trail?
What trail?
The trail from the woman
you did it with...
...to the woman you hope
never finds out you did it!
You always have to think
about the trail!
I don't think there's any trail.
Chloe works with that guy, Isaac.
Isaac's sister is Jasmine, and Jasmine
works at the massage place with Phoebe.
And Phoebe's friends with Rachel,
and that's the trail! I did it!
"After applying the Waxine
and linen strips to leg number one..."
- Did that!
- Okay.
"Grasp one of the linen strips
by its easy-grab tab...
...and pull it off in one quick,
pain-free motion."
Was it not "pain-free"?
No, it was pain-ful!
Oh, my God, they should call it
"Pain-zine, now with a little wax."
The girls in the satin nighties
on the commercial...
...don't seem to think it's that bad.
That's because their nerves are
deadened from being so stupid.
But, hey, you know, if you don't
believe me, please, be my guest.
Oh, my God!
Now aren't you glad we didn't
start with the bikini strips?
Chloe, hi.
Is this about me taking your watch?
- You took my watch?
- I'm sorry. I do that.
You keep it. Listen, did you
tell anyone about us?
Oh, no. I feel like it really isn't
anybody's business, you know?
Exactly. So you didn't mention
anything to Isaac, right?
- Oh, I tell Isaac everything.
- You do? Of course you do.
Hi, Isaac.
You know, we haven't actually met.
You dog!
Yes, I suppose I am a dog.
But see, I happen to have a girlfriend.
Oh, right, that Rachel chick
from the coffee place.
Yeah, that's the one.
Listen, I don't want to hurt her.
Oh, hey, man, I know. It doesn't
matter how much we love them.
Monogamy is too cruel a rule.
Yeah. Listen, can you keep this
information to yourself?
Oh, no problem, dude.
We gotta look out for each other.
We're the same, you and me.
Actually, no, we're not.
Yeah, we are.
No, we're not.
- Okay, we're not.
- Right.
But we are.
Fine. I just need to know that
you're not gonna tell your sister.
I can promise not to tell her again.
Jasmine? We met at Phoebe's
birthday party. I'm Ross Geller.
You did a bad thing!
- Yes, I did.
- Very bad!
- Very bad.
- Very, very bad!
I'm agreeing with you.
Listen, did you happen
to tell Phoebe yet?
- No.
- Okay, Jasmine...
...please. Please don't.
I love my girlfriend very much...
...and I want more than anything
to just work it out with her, okay?
All right.
Thank you. Thank you.
But you should probably talk
to my roommate.
I told him,
and he knows Phoebe too.
Who's your roommate?
Gunther!
Gunther, please tell me
you didn't say anything to Rachel...
...about me and the girl
from the copy place.
I'm sorry.
Was I not supposed to?
Okay, I got an idea. Why don't you
pull off mine, and I pull off yours?
Or, you pull of yours,
and I will leave mine on...
...because I think
I can make this look work.
Come on, Phoebe. We can do this.
- All right.
Okay.
- What is it?
- What's going on?
- We're all right.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- We were just waxing our legs.
- Off?
For your information...
...this happens to be a pain
like no man will ever experience.
I don't think you can make that
statement unless you've been kicked...
...in an area God only meant
to be treated nicely.
I think women just have a lower
threshold for pain than men, that's all.
I mean, come on,
it's just a little wax.
Oh, yeah? Come here.
Oh, that's mature.
Okay, fine.
So now what, I just pull it off?
That's right.
Okay, Tin Man.
Rachel, come on.
Talk to me. Please!
Talk to you?
I can't even look at you right now.
What?
Nothing. Nothing.
- Rachel said everything was okay.
- What are they talking about?
- Just get away from me!
- I made a mistake, okay?
A mistake? What were you trying
to put it in? Her purse?
Where did he put it?
Ross, you had sex with another woman!
Oh, my God!
I knew something had to be wrong...
...because my fingernails
did not grow at all yesterday.
Yeah, well, I guess they had a fight,
and he got drunk...
You guys knew about this
and you didn't tell us?
He has sex and we get hit
in our heads!
Know what? I want you to leave!
Just get out! Now!
I want to stay.
I want to talk about this.
Okay. All right. How was she?
- What?
- Was she good?
Don't answer that.
You said you wanted to talk about it.
Let's talk about it. How was she?
- She was...
- Awful.
- She was not good.
- Horrible. Nothing compared to you.
She was different.
Good different?
Nobody likes change.
- Just stop!
- What? Okay! Okay! Okay!
Should we do something?
Yeah. Never cheat on Rachel.
I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
I was disgusted with myself...
...and this morning
I was upset...
...and then I got your
message and I was so happy.
And all I wanted was to get her out
of my apartment...
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Wait a minute.
What time did your
little friend leave?
Oh, my God. She was there?
She was still there?
She was in there when I was in there?
Listen, the important thing is,
she meant nothing to me.
And yet she was worth
jeopardizing our relationship!
I didn't think there was
a relationship.
- I thought we were broken up.
- We were on a break.
That, for all I knew, could last forever.
That, to me, is a breakup.
You gonna get out of this
on a technicality?
I'm not trying to "get out"
of anything, okay?
I thought our relationship was dead.
Well, you sure had a hell of a time
at the wake.
You know what? I don't think
we should listen to this anymore.
What are you doing?
We can't go out there.
Why not? I'm hungry.
Because they'll know
we've been listening.
God! And to have to hear about it
from Gunther!
Like I wanted him to tell you?
I ran all over the place trying
to make sure that didn't happen!
Oh, that is so sweet.
I think I'm falling in love with you
all over again.
I think we can go out. They have
more important things to worry about.
We'll be fine.
Look, Rachel, I wanted to tell you.
I thought I should. I did.
And then Chandler and Joey
convinced me not to!
Wax the door shut.
We're never leaving.
Hi, it's Phoebe. Listen, someone has
to take my 9:00 with Mr. Rehak...
...because it's 9:15 now,
and I'm not there.
No, I'm in the middle
of a huge relationship fight, so...
Oh, that's all right.
It's not mine.
Don't you realize none of this would
ever have happened if I didn't think...
...at that same moment
you were having sex with Mark?
All right.
Let's say I had slept with Mark. Would
you have been able to forgive me?
Yes, I would.
You'd be okay if you knew...
...that Mark had kissed me,
and been naked with me...
...and made love to me?
Yes.
If you knew that our hot, sweaty,
writhing bodies were...
Okay, okay.
Yeah, I would have been devastated...
...but I would still want
to be with you.
Because, I mean, it's you.
What?
Come on, Rachel,
tell me what you're thinking.
I'm thinking...
...I'm gonna order a pizza.
Order a pizza, like...
..."I forgive you"?
Oh, man!
Pizza?
I like pizza.
Put olives on the pizza.
We could eat the wax! It's organic!
Oh, great. Food with hair on it.
No, not the used wax.
Because that would be crazy?
Could I get in on that?
Because I'm kind of hungry myself.
Fine.
Hi, yes, I'd like to order
a large pizza.
- No anchovies.
- With extra anchovies.
That's okay.
I'll pick them off.
And could you please chop some up
and just put it right in the sauce?
You can have the last piece
if you want.
Well, I should think so.
You slept with someone.
They're gonna get through this,
aren't they?
Yeah. Come on, it's Ross and Rachel.
They've got to.
What if they don't?
You think I need a new walk?
What?
Well, you know, I've been walking
the same way since high school.
You know how some guys walk into
a room and everybody takes notice?
I think I need a take-notice walk.
Are you actually saying these words?
What, now you're not even
talking to me?
Look, Rachel, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I was out of my mind.
I thought I'd lost you.
How insane must I have been
to do something like this?
I don't cheat, right?
That's not me. I'm not Joey!
Yeah, okay.
Hey!
It's 3 in the morning. They don't
know that I've come home yet.
You notice how neither one of them
are wondering where I am?
Yeah, you know, people
can be so self-involved.
You know what? I'm not the one
that wanted that break, okay?
You're the one that bailed on us.
You're the one...
...that ran the moment things
got a little rough.
- That's...
- That's what?
- That is neither here nor there.
- Here we are...
...in a tough spot again.
What do you want?
How do you want to handle it?
You want to fight for us or bail?
Look, I did a terrible,
stupid, stupid thing, okay?
And I'm sorry. I wish I could
take it back, but I can't.
I just can't see us throwing away
something we know is so damn good.
Rachel, I love you so much.
No, Ross! Don't!
You can't just kiss me and think
you're gonna make it all go away.
It doesn't work that way.
It doesn't just make it better.
Okay. Okay.
I think you should go.
What?
I really think you need to go now.
Okay. Okay.
This morning you said there was nothing
so big we couldn't work past it.
What the hell did I know?
There's got to be a way we
can work past this.
I can't imagine my life without you.
You know? Without...
Without these arms...
...and your face and heart...
...your good heart, Rach, and...
No.
I can't. You're a totally
different person to me now.
I used to think of you as somebody
that would never, ever hurt me.
Ever.
God, and now I can't stop
picturing you with her.
I can't. It doesn't matter what you
say or what you do.
It's just changed everything.
Forever.
This can't be it.
Then how come it is?
They've been quiet for a long time.
Maybe she killed him.
Let's go.
Is that your new walk?
No. I really have to pee.