Bye-bye.
I just got us reservations
at Michelle's...
...and tickets to The Music Man
to celebrate...
...our first holiday season
as a betrothed couple.
- "Betrothed."
- Betrothed couple.
- Hey!
- Hi!
Pheebs?
Skull?
Yeah, it's my mom's.
Oh, my God!
No, no, no. It's not my mom.
It belonged to my mom.
She used to put it out
every Christmas...
...to remind us that even though
it's Christmas, people still die.
And you can put candy in it.
- Hey.
Licorice?
Sure.
- I get Ben for the holidays this year.
- That's great!
- Are you gonna dress up as Santa?
- Nope.
I mean,
I know Susan does every year...
...but I want to take this year
to teach him about Hanukkah.
And maybe I could teach Ben...
...about the Christmas skull
and how people die.
You may need to use this year
to teach Ben about Phoebe.
Hey.
- Did you know he was in there?
- No.
- How long have we been home?
- About half an hour.
Lovely.
The One With The Holiday Armadillo
You know what I was thinking?
When we get married, are you gonna...
...change your last name to "Bing"?
No.
Why not?
"Bing" is weird.
Yeah, I know what you mean. Gellar!
Oh, hey, you guys.
Guess what. My landlord just called.
My apartment's gonna be ready soon.
So I guess I'll be moving out.
Phoebe, I'm gonna miss you.
Yes, you will be very sad.
- I gotta go tell Rachel the good news.
- You guys are gonna live together again?
- Yeah, why not?
- She's just having so much fun with Joey...
...I just assumed she'd still
be living with him.
Why do you think she's having
so much fun living with Joey?
No reason, except she...
...told me.
Really? She said she didn't want
to live with me?
No. No, she didn't say that.
I think you should talk to Monica now.
Phoebe, don't worry. I'm sure
she wants to live with you.
You're sure?
You're absolutely sure?
No, but I'll bet she probably does.
Oh, probably?
I don't like that word.
I know what "probably" really means.
Yeah, yeah.
"Oh, your mom
probably won't kill herself."
You know, "No, the funeral director
probably won't hit on you."
"Yeah, that nice couple probably
will adopt you. " Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
but I'm not hanging all my hopes...
...of Rachel and I living together
on "probably."
You gotta take care of yourself
in this world.
History teaches us nothing.
"Bing" doesn't seem so weird now,
does it?
Great, you're home.
Guess what Phoebe got me
for Christmas.
- Drums?
- No, drums!
Hi, could we get
two burritos to go, please?
I'm sorry. But not that sorry,
because you don't have to live with it.
We have a reservation under
the name Chandler Bing.
Okay, we'll have a table for you
in about 45 minutes.
Forty-five minutes? We have tickets
to The Music Man at 8.
I'm sorry.
Christmas is a very busy time, sir.
Is this because of the burrito thing?
- You need to give him money.
- Give him money? It was a joke!
No. To get a table. Places like this
are always shaking you down.
- Everybody wants a payoff.
- All right, calm down, O'Malley.
- I'll slip him some money.
- But you've got to be smooth about it.
Hey, I can be smooth.
We're in a bit of a hurry,
so if you could get us a table...
...a little quicker, I'd appreciate it.
- Of course, sir.
- Okay.
- How'd it go?
- Had the money in the wrong hand.
Hey. You don't feel...
...like you're gonna throw up, do you?
- No.
Well, I do. So let's...
So, Ben, you...
You know what holiday is coming up,
don't you?
Christmas.
Yeah, and you know what
other holiday is coming up?
Christmas Eve.
Yes, but also...
Hanukkah!
See, you're part Jewish,
and Hanukkah is a Jewish holiday.
Santa has reindeers that can fly.
Right, but on Hanukkah...
Hanukkah is a celebration
of a miracle.
See, years and years ago, there were
these people called the Maccabees.
Okay, that's right. Yes...
...but on Hanukkah, we sing:
Okay, it's not a contest.
When is Santa coming?
How about this year,
instead of Santa...
...we have fun celebrating Hanukkah?
No Santa?
Was I bad?
No. Oh, no, no. Hey, you weren't bad.
You've been very good, Ben.
- Santa's mad at me.
- No, hey, hey, come on.
Ben, Santa is not mad at you, okay?
You're his favorite little guy.
So Santa's coming?
Yes!
Santa's coming.
Will he bring me an ant farm?
Will you keep it at Mommy's?
- Okay.
- Then sure!
Maybe this slipping-him-money thing
is not gonna work.
Maybe we should just wait.
You're the one who said you would die
if you didn't see Music Man.
I didn't say "die."
I said "cry."
It's easy. Just keep it casual.
Give him a kind word,
shake his hand and give him the money.
- How do you know so much about this?
- I don't know.
Richard used to do it, didn't he?
We'd be eating our soup right now.
Mustached bastard.
Okay, those people just left. Come on.
Quick, give him the money.
Excuse me.
We're in a bit of a hurry.
Can we...?
So you like the drums.
That's great.
You know, I was worried that
they would create maybe...
...an unbearable living situation.
But, okay, well, apparently not.
So, yay!
Hey, Pheebs,
we already learned a song.
Ready? One, two, three, four.
Tequila!
That's fun.
Here you go.
Thank you, Gunther.
Put her there.
Definitely not easier with coins.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Pheebs.
- Hey.
Here. Now I only owe you 49.50.
Hey, Pheebs...
...if you want to get Joey a Christmas
present that disrupts the entire building...
...why not get him
something more subtle...
...like a wrecking ball...
...or a vial of smallpox
to release in the hallway?
It's not just the drum noise.
Every five minutes...
...Joey throws his sticks
in the air...
...and I have to hear:
"Oh, my eye! Oh, God, my eye!"
- I mean, it is so annoying.
- Yes, thank you.
You see, this is how normal people
are supposed to react to drums.
Phoebe, you got Joey drums
to annoy Rachel...
...so she wouldn't want
to live there anymore?
Maybe on some level.
Joey, you know that you could just
not throw the sticks up in the air.
What is rock 'n' roll about that?
Hey, Joey, I got you another present.
Hold it!
Before you tell me what it is...
Okay, what is it?
It's a...
...tarantula!
God, Rachel, I'm sorry.
What was I thinking...
...giving Joey this big, gross,
scary spider...
...in such a poorly constructed cage?
What are you talking about?
I love them.
I had a tarantula when I was a kid.
But it died because my cat ate it.
And then my cat died.
But, Joey, isn't this cool?
Is it on me?
I feel like it's on me. I got...
Oh, isn't that adorable?
Joey is afraid of the tarantula.
He's so adorable.
God, he's just so much fun.
Joey's the best. I'm glad
you're having so much fun here.
Wait a minute.
What's the matter?
Our apartment is ready.
And that makes you angry because...?
Because you'd rather
live here with Joey.
- Where did you get that?
- Monica and Chandler...
...said that you were having
so much fun here...
...and apparently no amount of drums
or tarantula is gonna change that.
Phoebe,
did you get all this stuff for Joey...
...to try and drive me out
of the apartment?
You might as well have just
gotten him a fish.
You know how fish freak me out.
Fish.
But it wouldn't have mattered.
You and I are gonna live together.
We're roommates.
That's the deal.
Yes, but I wanted you to want
to live with me.
But, okay, if you're having
so much fun over here...
It's so much more fun with you.
- We did have fun, didn't we?
- We had so much fun.
Remember the time we were playing
with the SuperBall...
...and we accidentally threw it through
the window and it broke?
I remember paying for the window,
but I don't remember how it broke.
Yeah, stuff like that.
Well, anyway, they say, if we want,
we could see it tonight.
- I would love to.
- Yay, okay!
- Good, good, good.
- Great. All right. Good.
And Monica asked me
to make the drumming stop.
Done.
Hello, sir.
You here to return those pants?
No, these are my pants.
Okay.
- How can I help you?
- Do you have a Santa outfit left?
Two days before Christmas?
Sorry, man.
- Did you try Costume City?
- Yeah, I've tried everywhere.
- Please, please. I mean, I'll pay extra.
- Sorry. But...
...I do have 74 of them
coming back on the 26th.
Okay, look.
Do you have anything Christmas-y?
I promised my son, and I really
don't want to disappoint him.
Come on, you gotta have something.
I'm the Holiday Armadillo!
I'm a friend of Santa's...
...and he sent me here to wish you...
...a merry Christmas!
What happened to Santa,
Holiday Armadillo?
Santa was unavailable...
...so close to Christmas.
Come in, have a seat.
You must be exhausted,
coming all the way from Texas.
- Texas?
- That's right, Ben.
I'm Santa's representative...
...for all the Southern states.
And Mexico!
But Santa sent me here...
...to give you these presents, Ben.
Maybe the lady will help me
with these presents.
Wow, thanks!
You're welcome, Ben.
Merry Christmas.
And happy Hanukkah!
Are you for Hanukkah too?
Because I'm part Jewish.
You are? Me too.
Because armadillos
also wandered in the desert?
You want to wander in the hall?
Hey, Ben!
What if the Holiday Armadillo...
...told you all about
the Festival of Lights?
Cool!
Come on, Ben.
Years and years ago...
...there were these people called...
...the Maccabees!
- Ho, ho, ho!
Merry Christmas!
- Santa!
- Hey!
What are you doing here, Santa?
Well, I'm here to see
my old buddy Ben.
What are you doing here...
...Weird Turtle Man?
I'm the Holiday Armadillo...
...your part-Jewish friend.
You sent me here
to give Ben some presents.
Remember?
What?
Did you bring me any presents, Santa?
You bet I did, Ben.
Put her there.
Well, it would have worked this time
if his hands weren't so damn small.
Ho, ho, ho!
Ben, why don't you come open
more presents.
Santa, the armadillo and I
will have a talk in the kitchen.
There's a sentence
I never thought I'd say.
What are you doing?
You called everyone and said you were
having trouble finding a Santa costume...
...so I borrowed one
from a guy at work.
Thank you, but you gotta leave.
- Why?
- Because...
...I'm finally getting him excited
about Hanukkah...
...and you're wrecking it.
But I didn't get to shake my belly
like a bowlful of jelly.
I'm sorry, Chandler,
but this is really important to me.
Fine, I'll give the suit back.
Hey, you think you can keep it
another night?
Santa? Really?
Yeah, is that okay?
Did your dad ever dress up like Santa?
- No.
- Then it's okay!
Okay, Ben. Santa has to go.
Say goodbye.
No, why does he have to go?
Because if Santa and the Holiday...
...Armadillo...
...are ever in the same room
for too long...
...the universe will implode!
Merry Christmas!
No, why can't the armadillo leave?
I want Santa.
Fine, I give up. Santa...
Santa can stay!
Well, I'll stay...
...but only because I want to hear
about Hanukkah.
Ben, will you sit here with Santa...
...and learn about Hanukkah?
Okay, Santa.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
All right, it's time...
...for the story of Hanukkah.
Years and years ago...
...there were these people
called the Maccabees!
Merry Christmas!
Oh, wow, look at this place!
Oh, this is terrible.
They've made so many changes...
...I can't even feel
my grandmother's presence anymore.
Oh, new sconces!
- Oh, my God!
- What?
Okay, remember how you told me that
your grandmother put up that wall...
...to make that into two bedrooms?
- Yeah.
And that the landlord
might find out...
...and then tear it down?
- Yeah?
Do you really not know
where I'm going with this?
No, of course I do. What?
It left. It's one huge room.
Oh, no!
Wow!
See?
I guess we'll just have to
put the wall back up.
- You can't, because of the new skylight.
- There's a skylight?
Wow!
So, what should we do? Should
we start looking for a new place?
You know, I'm sensing...
...that my grandmother
would not be comfortable with that.
Oh, yeah?
Starting to feel her again there,
are we?
- A little bit. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Pheebs, is your grandmother maybe
saying that you should live here alone?
You heard it too? You have the gift.
Phoebe, it's okay.
I like living with Joey.
- Are you sure?
- Please. I hate packing...
...it's closer to work.
And we do have fun.
Although, I'm really gonna miss
living with you.
- Oh, me too.
- I know.
Oh, wait. Did you hear that?
Listen. I'm getting something
from your grandmother.
She said that since you get to keep
the one-bedroom apartment...
...you should give Rachel
the purple chair.
No, I do not hear that.
Oh, no, wait a minute. Oh, okay.
She didn't say "chair," she said "share." You
should share the one-bedroom apartment.
Oh, the purple chair.
No, yeah, I heard that.
And the miracle was that
that little bit of oil...
...that should have lasted
just one day, burned for...
- Eight whole days.
- That's right.
And that's why we celebrate
Hanukkah today. The end.
- Awesome.
- Yeah.
My favorite part...
...was when Superman
flew all the Jews out of Egypt.
The armadillo was actually
not so thrilled about that part.
Why is Santa kissing Aunt Monica?
Because Aunt Monica
was very, very good this year.
Okay, Ben, it's time to light...
...the Hanukkah candles!
Hey.
Wow! Looks like the Easter Bunny's
funeral in here.
Come on, come on.
We're lighting the candles.
I understand why Superman is here...
...but why is there a porcupine
at the Easter Bunny's funeral?
- Did you get it?
- I got it.
Is it back in the cage?
It's back in the cage.
Is the cage closed?
Joey, will you just come out here
and stop being such a baby!